In other
local news, one of the heads
of the notorious
Frost crime family,
Walt Frost, was exonerated
on methamphetamines
charges today,
ending a 17-month
legal battle
with the state of Arkansas.
Walt's brother Donny Frost
was exonerated himself
on drug trafficking charges
tied to cocaine
and Colombia cartels
just last year.
Thankfully, the state
has seen a recent lull
in what has been
a decade-long feud
with the Frost family,
leaving some
to speculate that...
- Hey, Henry.
- Got Lucas Frost here for Ray Frost.
- You got the time?
- 10:15.
Thank you.
- Oh, hey, sweetheart.
- Hey, Mom.
- Dickey.
- Your uncle Donny was here.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
So many Frosts coming
in and out of this place.
We should start charging
the family rent.
Good luck collecting.
- You visit him yet?
- No.
You want me to pass him
along anything?
Tell him happy birthday.
Okay. So, nothing, right?
- Mm-hmm.
- Okay.
- Frost.
- Hey.
You got 30.
Oh, I will never forget
my birthday
because it's the only day
you come see me.
- Happy birthday.
- What's this?
Deer jerky.
I thought you weren't
allowed to hunt.
What?
I'm getting married.
Good. Any thought to kids?
I think it'll
come quick after, yeah.
Good, good, good.
Carrying on the Frost name,
that's important.
What's wrong?
Come on, say it.
Nothing's wrong.
Um, I'm just gonna be--
I'm gonna be moving on.
Moving on?
What does that mean?
So I'm not gonna be bringing
my kids around here.
Wow, you--
you are a piece of work,
bringing this shit to me
on my birthday.
Sorry, I thought you'd--
you'd understand, that's all.
Sit down.
Sit the fuck down!
There was this old
Pentecostal man.
I used to see him
out in his front yard
waving a rattlesnake
around by the neck.
He always used to say
the spirit in him was so great
that he couldn't get bit.
Well that snake reared up,
bit him square in the forehead one day.
Son of a bitch dropped dead,
15 minutes flat.
Now, that rattlesnake
could have chosen not to bite
a thousand times or more,
but the venom--
the venom was always there.
You are a rattlesnake, son.
Just like me.
Hey, you don't know me, Ray.
Goodbye, Ray.
Excuse me, ma'am.
I was wondering
if I could open an account.
Okay, what kind of account
would you like to open?
I'm actually,
uh, getting married.
- Oh, congratulations.
- Oh, thank you.
- Thank you so much.
- Yeah.
And I was wondering,
do you do joint accounts?
- Yeah, we do.
- Oh, wonderful.
- Well, I have money.
- How much?
I got enough.
Actually, uh, more than enough.
- Okay. Tell me about her.
- Okay, um,
- she got beautiful eyes.
- Okay. What color?
I think brown.
And sort of a cute smile,
and maybe an unbelievable ass--
- Sense of humor?
- Sense of humor.
That's what I was gonna say.
I was gonna say sense of humor.
- Sometimes I stutter.
- See, joint accounts are very complicated,
and I need to prove to my boss
that this thing is real.
- You know what I mean?
- Okay. Yeah, yeah.
It's a conundrum that
you're in right now, yeah.
- It's hard.
- Um.
Is there anything I can do
to prove it?
Yes. I am going
to need a deposit.
- Okay.
- A really big one.
- Oh.
- That is in the form of a...
embarrassing act of love
and devotion.
I feel like you have
something in mind.
- No, I do. Yeah, yeah.
- Oh, no. Come on.
Emma. What are you writing?
- What are you-- what are you writing?
- Zz-zzt.
Oh, dear God.
Come on, Mr. Frost.
No. Hey, hey. Hey! Hey!
Excuse me, everyone.
I'm sorry to bother you
in this moment,
but I have something to say.
I, Lucas Frost, am madly in love
with Emma Elizabeth Darling.
She is the light of my life,
the moon to my sun,
the beat in my heart.
Without her brilliance,
I would be lost forever.
She is real,
she is honest to a fault,
um, and she's my best friend.
I'm so lucky
to be marrying you.
And also, I'm the sexiest son of a bitch
in all of Arkansas.
- I did not write that.
- Yes, she did.
She did write that.
Thank you.
♪ Take away my blues
♪ Listen, everybody's
gotta be somewhere ♪
♪ Whether its cloudy
or whether its fair ♪
♪ Every day's a lovely day
to spend the day with you ♪
...perfect flower girl.
Could you imagine her in that little dress?
Oh, my gosh.
Think she'd be up for it?
I'm just scared she's gonna
eat all the flowers.
- Hear that?
- Yeah. It's okay.
- They're getting worse.
- Yeah.
You're unbelievable. Oh, my schedule, huh?
/ Yeah!
And what do you do all day?
You're just out back doing nothing?
Why? Because you question me about
every fucking thing! / You are unbelievab--
- Hey.
Hey. Sorry about that.
You good? / You really didn't have
to do that, you know?
- It was on the way.
- Hey. How you doing?
- Oh, I'm sorry about that.
- You want some coffee?
Yes, actually.
I would love some coffee.
- Ooh, I'll take one.
- Yeah?
-No sugar this time.
-Yeah, I got you.
- Uh...
- Sorry.
Banks these days. Pushing people out
left and right, you know?
Really ain't fair.
No offense, Emma.
I'm gonna go talk to him.
How you doing?
- I'm tired.
- Yeah. I know.
Got her off of Wyn Carson.
Sucker shoots straight
as all get out.
Too bad you're a cross-eyed
son of a bitch.
Come on, see it.
Thank you.
Whoo.
Yeah, that's nice.
Went and saw Ray today.
Yeah? And?
Broke the news.
Told him I wasn't coming around no more.
He ain't the bad guy
you think he is.
It's Mom. She got you brainwashed
into thinking all that.
Naw, I'm not brainwashed.
So he killed a couple cartel.
Big whoop.
This drug shit, you think I want my kids
growing up around all that?
I bought you some groceries.
Man, you didn't have
to do that.
- I know. I know.
- We're fine.
Yeah.
I'm gonna-- I'm gonna get 'er
done like I always do.
As long as you're not thinking about
working for the family again or--
- Donny.
- You may be my brother,
- I'm still a half-blood.
- I'm just being serious about it.
You think I hit a rough patch, I got to go
running to the head of your family?
That or something else,
and I'm just...
What?
You clean?
No, come on.
Don't walk off all pissed.
Tuck!
We still going to Bryce's race?
Oh, he does!
Bryce Frost up
to the number two spot.
And here he goes!
He's been going a little hot.
Here comes Frost!
And he's passing...
The kid is a genius
in those turns.
- Kind of reminds me of you.
- I'm sorry.
Can you say that again?
Did you just call me a genius?
- No.
- Ma, you hear that?
Mm-mm. No.
How's the planning coming?
Oh, we just picked out
the flowers.
-Oh, yeah? What kind?
- Hydrangeas.
- Oh! I love hydrangeas!
- Tuck, can you get me a Coke?
Make Lucas get it.
I'm watching the race.
- I'm watching the race.
- I'll go.
- No, Tuck'll get it.
- She just said she'd get it.
-Tuck, just go! Go!
- I'm not asking again now.
Yeah, this is the reason
there ain't a man alive
who can put up with you.
Tuck!
- Yeah? What? What?
- Are you kidding me?
Real gentleman you raised.
Half of one at least.
Well, half is better than
you can hope for,
- sweetheart, in a man.
- Come on.
Here we go.
Tuck! Tuck!
- Where you going?
- I can't deal with her, man.
She's always doing that shit,
you know? You see it.
She's just-- just needling me,
man, for no reason.
- No, she doesn't.
- Hey, does she not?
I mean, yeah, a little bit.
- Really?
- Yeah, yeah.
- All the time.
- Oh, shit.
-Who's that?
- That's Sid.
Is he a Frost?
I've never seen him before.
He's my cousin.
Tall one's his brother Eli.
- They're Walt's boys.
- Something ain't right about him.
I mean, he's been
in Tucker since '88.
- Stabbed his old man.
- '87.
You don't get out in five
on felony aggravated.
He was dealing.
Nothing but a peacock.
- Hey, hey.
- Hmm?
Don't worry about him, baby.
Okay?
- Okay.
- Get him up.
- Come on, Tuck.
- No, I'm good.
Come on,
let's go get you a pop.
A little pop.
You want some popcorn? Huh?
Almost had me on that lap,
too, but I--
Gotta start
from the back next time.
- Next week.
- You're gonna kill it.
- I'm proud of you.
- Are you gonna be here? Gonna be here?
- Yeah, I am.
- All right.
- Love you, boy.
- Love you.
- Give me some.
- Good job, Bryce!
- Bryce!
- ♪ I feel so good
♪ With you, baby
- Get in there. Get in there.
-
- Woohoo!
- Keep it up.
- ♪ Life makes no promise
- ♪ Makes no promise
♪ How it's gonna turn out
♪ It's ups and downs
for everyone ♪
♪ Oh, baby
♪ Future and sweet
surprises ♪
♪ Surprise
Hey.
Come on. Coffee time.
Coffee time.
I don't-- no, it's too early.
Why are you making me up?
Well, I have to deliver
those checks today.
You're driving.
- Hey.
- What the hell happened to you?
No, man, I gone and got sick.
I already called in.
I'm just gonna, you know,
take it easy today.
Oh, come on. My ass. You're gonna
make me cut twice as much today?
Hey, don't act like I don't cover for
your ass all the time.
Don't do that.
Come on! Tuck!
Baby, can you hand me
those checks?
- Bateland Scrapyard?
- Yeah.
Do you think we need
all them flowers or...?
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Oh. Okay.
But all of them?
Every single one of those
flowers, I want.
Okay. Then you'll get
every single one of them.
♪ All through the years
♪ Through laughter
and tears ♪
♪ Once in awhile
Tony, the hell you doing in here
and not on that Pinto?
Yeah, I don't think
I'm gonna work on Fords anymore.
And I told you,
I don't go by Tony anymore.
- Just "T."
- You're not wearing a pound
of gold chains around
your dang neck here, Tony.
I let you strip shitboxes
'cause I know your daddy.
Bring your own water
from now on.
That cooler's for the girls.
- Morning, Emma.
- Morning, Merle.
Just toss those checks
on Anna's desk.
- She's running late.
- Okay.
- Hey, Tony.
- What's up, Emma?
- You doing all right?
- Yeah.
That's good.
Nobody fucking move!
Get to the safe! Hurry!
- You get the safe?
- Yeah, I got it!
Get her up.
Get her the fuck up!
- Come on. Get up.
- No.
- Get her up, man!
Just stay calm, we'll get out
of your pretty hair.
...scattered showers thunder showers
Tuesday late in the day.
Partly sunny, brighter,
drier Wednesday and Thursday.
- You don't have to do this.
- Shut the fuck up!
Hey, hey, hey, can you just
take it down the notch?
Get your finger off
the trigger.
Sorry.
"Amazing Grace," you know it?
The song. The fucking song.
Do you know it?
- Yeah. Yeah.
- We're gonna sing it, okay?
♪ Amazing grace
♪ How sweet the sound
♪ That saved a wretch like me
Keep it going.
♪ I once was lost
- ♪ But now I'm...
- I got one.
♪ Was blind, but now I see
Jesus, how fucking long
does this take?
- ♪ 'Twas grace that taught me
- Can you hurry it up?
- I'm going as fast as I can!
- Well, fucking go faster!
♪ And grace my fear relieved
- We got two.
- You looking at her?
- No.
- Why are you looking at her?
- I'm not doing nothing.
- Why don't you look at this?
Don't move.
Don't fucking move!
We got--
Oh, fuck.
It just came out itself.
What the fuck's the matter with you?
What the fuck is the matter with you?
- I didn't mean to do it. It just came out.
- You fucking--
- I didn't do it on purpose.
- You fucking idiot!
- Don't-- you fucking idiot!
- It just came out. It just came out.
- Let's go! We got the money.
- Let's go! Let's go!
Leave, leave, leave!
Let's go, man! Let's go!
Emma? Emma!
Emma! What happened?
- What happened?
-I don't know.
Emma, Emma, Emma!
Baby! Baby! Hey!
Oh, God. Call 911!
Do something, please.
Hey, baby, baby, baby.
- Hey, hey! Hey, do--
- We need help!
Do you have a-- baby! Baby!
- Baby, come on.
- Send someone now please!
- Wake up. Wake up!
- Please!
Help! Get help! Get help!
Come on, baby.
Baby, come on, wake up.
Get help!
- Tucker. How's he doing?
- Darlene.
Well, he' right there in the kitchen.
Go ask him yourself.
- Any leads?
- Not that I can discuss.
- Get back in the car, Dickle.
- Don't do that, Tuck.
It's Dickey. You know that.
I want to talk to my mother.
Now get back in the goddamn car.
- Tuck.
- I'll be in the car.
Thank you. / Did you find Eli yet?
Tell me what's going on.
It looks like he skipped town.
I really can't talk
about the investigation.
Hey, I'm asking my mother now.
Not the cop.
- What do we know?
- I can't talk about it.
Honey.
We will find out who did this.
We will.
We're gonna get Eli.
I promise you.
Okay? You boys are just
gonna have to be patient.
- Mm-hmm?
- Mm.
Your Uncle Donny's
here to see you.
Wanted to come by,
give our condolences
and so forth.
Why are you here?
There's been a meeting...
...between both sides
of the family.
Walt was there.
Think you should know
what he said.
Okay, what'd he say?
He's claiming their side had
nothing to do with the robbery.
- Eli wasn't at the scrapyard.
- He was there.
Not according to Walt.
Eli was there.
This was your granddaddy's.
You should have it. / What is that for?
He named Walt's son at the scene
of an armed robbery and a murder.
You'll want to be prepared.
Wait a second.
They ain't going after Lucas.
Come on, now.
We all know Sid killed her.
No, instead you're too busy
tiptoeing around Walt
like he's some
goddamn boogeyman!
Why do you fucking care?
You're not a Frost.
Only reason you're here is because of him.
/ Hey!
We're here to help Lucas
in case you forgot.
You're a good kid.
And you're also
my brother's son.
And I'll be there for you
till the day I die.
But I can't go starting
another war right now,
even if I think one of them boys
pulled the trigger.
It's just bad for business.
With all due respect...
I think it was the family
business that killed Emma.
I don't need the fucking gift.
Night, y'all.
Talk some goddamn sense
into him.
Don't look at me like that.
At this time
on this morning...
...I will read the 23rd Psalm.
"The Lord is my shepherd.
I shall not want.
He maketh me to lie down
in green pastures,
and leadeth me beside
the still waters.
He restoreth my soul,
and leadeth me in the paths
of righteousness
for His name's sake.
Yea, though I walk through
the valley of the shadow..."
Cool it. Honey.
"Yeah, though I walk through the valley
of the shadow of death,
I will fear no evil,
for Thou art with me.
Thy rod and thy staff,
they comfort me.
Thou preparest a table before me
in the presence of mine enemies.
Thou will anointest
my head with oil.
My cup runneth over."
In the face of this tragedy
that has rocked our community,
it's very hard for me to stand up here
this morning... / No, no.
...when just a few days ago
I was seated in this...
Sid!
Where's Eli?
Say that again.
That's my little brother, Lucas.
You don't think I'm gonna have
something to say about that?
- I just want Eli.
- Listen to me.
You spent too much time gallivanting around
with that girl in the box,
so clearly you weren't
paying attention.
You mess with one person
on this side of the family,
you're gonna open up
a whole can of worms.
You gotta mind
the hungry ones, man.
That's my advice to you.
Motherfucker hungry enough,
he'll eat just about anything.
Mind the hungry ones!
Oh, shoot, this comes--
this comes back on us,
that means
it's coming back on you.
You heard every word I said.
I want you to take
half the shipment,
you're gonna sprinkle it around.
You know what?
I got visitors here.
I'm gonna have to call
you back later.
Let me get a burger, no cheese,
pickles and onion, mayo on the side.
Boss? What are we doing?
I'm ordering a burger.
What are you doing?
Shouldn't we go talk to him?
Make it two. To go, please.
Pardon me.
Thank you.
- You go wait in the car.
- What?
I'll get the food.
Go wait in the car.
Hi there. / How's that investigation
moving along, deputy?
What's it like being a cop?
I've always been wondering.
I find it real fascinating
what you do.
Chasing down the bad guys,
playing cowboys and Indians.
- Must be fun.
- Well, there's nothing fun
about dealing with murderers
and child molesters.
Remind me what it is
you do again.
- Importing and exporting.
- What kind of goods?
All kinds. You know
what the most important
- part of doing business is?
- Accounting?
Letting people know
how serious you are.
- Do you know how you do that?
- Guess you're gonna tell me.
Fear.
See, fear is really the only way
to make people understand
that you mean business.
And I take business
very seriously.
Well, look at me.
Just preaching
to the choir now, aren't I?
I don't need fear to do my job.
I have the law.
Ah, that's where you're wrong.
Ain't no different for a cop.
Business is business.
If someone gets in your way,
you get them out of your way.
'Cause all it takes is one
itsy bitsy little finger
to make an example of someone.
And then, shit, who knows
what you're capable of?
Ain't that right?
We do have something in common.
- Mm.
- You and I are both destroyers.
And what you gotta do is you got
to ask yourself, who's it gonna be?
Who am I gonna
make an example of
so that everybody else out there
knows that I mean business?
24.
Looks like it's you.
Bye, now.
The number
of your last incoming call
was 501-154-3210.
501-154-32--
Operator?
Yeah, I'd like an address
for 501-154-3210.
Get the ball for Mama.
I'm gonna come get you!
Ellie!
- Can I help you?
- Hey, there.
- Are you Lou Byers?
- Yeah. Who are you?
I'm Deputy Woodley,
Sheriff's Department. Can I come in?
You know, it's a mess in here.
Why don't I come out there?
Oh, I have seen worse.
- Well, the reason I'm here...
- Yeah, let me guess.
- Eli Frost.
- Ah.
Come on now, I heard about
that scrapyard job.
And I know you're here 'cause you got your
little paperwork on me and Eli.
- Mm.
- But what your filing cabinet
don't say is
I did a goddamn year
for that son of a bitch.
Eli Frost can rot
for all I care.
You want to find him,
start at Ketcham Mill.
- That's where he cooks.
- Ketcham Mill?
- That's the place out off 300?
- Yeah, that's it.
There's a deer stand
back there.
400 yards deep,
you'll find the lean-to they cook at.
That's way out there, ain't it?
A lot of work
moving inventory down 300.
You're the detective.
- I'm just doing my civic duty here.
- Mm.
- Mind if I use the bathroom?
- First door on the right.
- Tuck!
- What?
Tuck, someone left a box.
Ellie saw it move.
- What's in it?
- No idea, but there's something in there.
Hey! Excuse me.
You want to snoop
around my property,
you can come back
with a freaking warrant.
I'll do that, Mr. Byers.
Thanks for your time.
We have to be careful
not to jump
to any conclusions.
Did you see anyone?
Anyone at all?
- No, I was with Ellie.
-Get your things.
We're gonna move everyone
up to the lake house.
Come on, let's go.
Should we go play
somewhere outside?
Get your motherfucking
hands up in the air!
- What the fuck are you doing here?
- Put 'em down!
- Get your fucking guns down!
Guns down on the ground
right now!
- Hands in the fucking air!
- Can everybody calm the fuck down?
Let's put our guns down.
Eli, let's show 'em
how it's done.
You know what?
Put it on the ground.
Put the gun on the ground.
I don't talk business with guns.
That's nice, right?
We can talk like adults.
- Where's Holt?
- Holt's out.
Long story short,
Holt's retired.
I'm ready to be
your new supplier.
There are lines in the sand.
You know that,
and your father knows that.
Donny, the world's changing.
I'm giving you the opportunity
to be a part of that change.
I want to do business.
Me and you.
He might have been the one
that murdered Emma.
And you, you're crazy if you think
I want to do business with you.
You know what?
That's funny.
Come on,
let me take care of it.
It's all right.
I'm gonna handle it.
Yeah.
I'm done chewing the rag.
Starts to taste bad
after a while.
- Take it or leave it.
- Take it or leave it?
Mm-hmm.
Here's my deal.
Go fuck yourself.
God damn--
What the--
Ah.
What the fuck? / Ah! Well, I mean,
he should have taken the deal.
Listen, don't worry about it.
It was just a matter of time anyway.
What the fuck?
We don't have time to clean all this stuff.
- We gotta get out of here now.
- Okay, Eli, Eli.
Call Reed.
Tell him to get Fiddle,
- get over here and clean up the bodies.
- Wait a minute--
You and Lou,
take everything to his house.
- Wait a minute, where are you going?
-Home.
We can't move
all this in one trip.
Well, take multiple trips,
you incestuous fucking doughnut.
Oh, shit.
Jesus, he's really damn heavy.
What do we do with these guys?
I say we toss them.
Yeah, might as well.
Saves us another trip.
I think it's pretty obvious.
Sid is trying to expand
outside the family.
- You think Walt has any idea?
- Shut up.
What the fuck was that?
There's someone here!
Go, go, go!
Over here!
No, he's running! Go, go!
Heading out the back!
Shit!
Fiddle! Reed!
It's me.
I'm not going anywhere.
I didn't-- was just at the wrong place
the wrong time.
I promise.
Well, what do we do? We gotta kill him,
right? / Man, would you shut up
- and let me think?
- You thinking too slow, dude.
- Boys, boys, boys. Listen.
- This isn't my problem.
- Just calm down, okay?
- No, this is yours.
I gotta clean up
and get shit over to Byers.
Reed! Reed!
Fiddle. Fiddle, look.
I'm so sorry. I didn't--
I didn't know--
- Turn around. Turn around!
- It's okay.
Turn. Turn around.
- I didn't see nothing.
- I don't care. Go.
Come on, Fiddle.
I'm not gonna say nothing
to no one, okay?
- Just stop talking.
- We-- we're family.
So you think your gun changed
Frederick Carson, hmm?
- Who says I pointed a gun?
- I do.
Oh, shit.
- Are they up?
- What is that?
Listen, I need you
to be cool about this.
Jesus Christ.
Where'd you get this?
I stumbled across Fiddle
and Reed.
They were doing
some sort of deal.
- I mean, they were moving bodies.
- What bodies?
I don't know.
I didn't get to see them.
I had to get out of there
as fast as I could.
And what,
you take the fucking drugs?
I didn't know
what else to do, okay?
At least I'm doing something
instead of sitting around here.
We're laying low, man. That's what
we're doing. This was the plan.
Listen, listen, listen.
Walt only deals with meth.
- That's coke.
- Okay, so?
That means they're
going behind Walt's back.
Walt doesn't know about this.
- We bring it to him.
- That's your plan?
Yes. / You're gonna walk up to
Walt fucking Frost,
- acting like you're--
- Don't fucking laugh at me right now.
Are you goddamn serious?
At least I'm trying to do something.
Hey. What the hell
is going on out here?
- Ellie's trying to sleep.
- Sorry. Yeah, sorry.
We don't say a goddamn word
about this to anybody.
Okay.
Mom does her job,
this shit disappears.
Trust me.
I trust you. Yeah.
What?
Bryce.
Found his body out
at the river.
Cousin Jeb and Uncle Donny, too.
Lucas.
Lucas, wait a minute.
- I'm sick of waiting.
- No, listen, honey.
I understand, but you just
can't do something stupid.
What's stupid? What is stupid?
Tell me! Tell me!
Stop, stop! Wake up!
Nothing is getting done!
- I'm doing everything I can.
- You keep saying that.
You keep saying you do everything you can.
/ I am doing everything I can.
- Our side of the family's dying.
- What are you talking about?
- Sweetheart, you listen--
- He was 18!
Yes, I know. I know,
and we're doing everything
we can to try and fix this.
I know it. Lucas!
You coming? / If you go after them,
I can't protect you!
- Tuck. Don't. Don't go with him.
- I love you.
- Howdy.
- What you boys needing?
My brother and I are thinking
about going hunting.
Y'all never been hunting? Y'all must be
from Little Rock or something.
Yeah, let's see here.
Here's your 12 gauge,
all-purpose.
Probably where
you want to start.
He looks a little light.
You might want
to watch the kick.
What kind of shells
you recommend?
Well, what kind of hunting
you mostly doing?
Duck and deer.
Well, slugs are for deer.
Birdshot's for duck.
Cannons, 500.
Slugs are seven for five.
I do cash only here.
And this is-- this is how
you load it, right?
- Yeah.
- Now that's a chambered.
- Yeah?
- Yep. There you go.
Hey, whoa.
- What the hell's this now?
- I want to talk to Walt.
Boy, you think it's the first time
I ever been staring down one of them?
- Might be the last.
- Take it easy.
You got to use this phone over here
to let him know you're here.
Just...
Hey, hey.
Nice and easy, big boy.
Yeah. Tell Walt he's got
some visitors here.
Couple of young fellas.
I've never seen them.
Uh-huh. All right.
I'll pass that along.
God damn it!
Hey! Put it down!
Put it down!
I just want to talk
to Walt, okay?
- This one got cute.
-God damn!
We don't need the same
for you two.
Grab the bag.
Fi fi fo fum,
I smell the blood of...
...my own kind.
I don't think I've seen you
since you was like knee-high.
How's your old man doing?
I didn't come here
to talk about Ray.
- I came to make a deal.
- A deal. All right.
Well, usually, you know,
when I'm talking business,
I like to put
all of the guns away.
Put your goddamn guns away.
Everybody, put them away!
That's it.
God damn.
You more of a man
I figured you for.
Look at you.
You stout. Stout.
Yeah, a little tense, but...
I came to settle things
with you.
You a settler, huh?
I like that. Ambitious, too.
I like that, to a point.
Now, I'm guessing
that has something to do
with that mystery bag on you.
It's cocaine.
I'm-- I'm giving it to you.
- It's all yours.
- No, no, no.
It ain't mine or yours.
Things, you know, change hands,
but they ain't ever fully owned.
See, what it is
is you offer me
something you got
that I might want
for something I got
you must really want.
Oh, boy.
Ah. That's how
all this works, right?
I guess.
Whatever the fuck you do,
don't guess. Be sure.
See, I got to know
that I can trust your word
with this deal
we're talking about.
- So, you guess?
- I'm not guessing. I'm telling you.
What you come to tell me, boy?
That you want to trade this here cocaine?
- Yes, sir.
- To settle things?
- As long as we agree on terms.
- Whoa! Hot damn, son!
That's good! Now--
now we're getting somewhere.
I'm gonna tell you what.
You're like pulling teeth, boy.
So, terms. All right.
What are the terms
for this deal
to beat all deals?
The cocaine for what?
I want Eli.
Mm.
Yeah, well, I know you
a bit new at all this,
but I think you better
go back and ask ol' Ray...
...what the street price
of dope is.
'Cause in my humble opinion,
he's overpricing.
Might be just outright gouging.
Fiddle and Reed were moving
the coke at the barge facility,
along with bodies.
But you know that
already, right?
Because Sid and Eli are trying
to go behind your back,
trying to take our side
of the business.
But you would never let your
boys undermine you, would you?
Why the fuck should I believe
anything you say?
Because Donny...
Jeb...
...and Bryce are all dead.
And that leaves our side
of the business to me,
so you deal with me.
All right, then.
I'll deal with you.
I want to give you all of it.
The dope business?
The entire business.
The fuck are you up to, boy?
I just want Eli
and nothing else.
You sure are nothing like your daddy,
I'll give you that.
You have an opportunity...
...to be the head
of the entire business, all united.
It's never happened before.
I need to go, uh,
check on my brisket.
Your boys are welcome to join
if you want to.
Fiddle.
You know who T.R. Frost was?
No.
He was your
great-great-grandfather.
Last head of the family.
Died in 1929,
killed by his own kind.
You really should know
your history.
So you'll be the first head
of the family since 1929.
We got a deal?
Yeah, yeah. Sure.
All right.
All right, we got a deal.
No, we ain't got a fucking deal.
Not when you come to my house
and fuck with my boys.
Piece of shit.
-Cocaine?
- It wasn't us.
Oh, yeah.
I don't care who it was.
You're not only putting this
investigation in jeopardy,
- you're putting me in jeopardy.
- Uncle Walt is the direction
- we're trying to--
- No, no. I don't want to hear that name.
This is about you
and your brother.
Just get this shit over with.
Book us already.
What is it with you?
Why do you have to hate me so much?
I never said I hated you.
You got that from him.
What the fuck are you talking--
- This is not about him.
- It's always about him.
I'm just the one
you had by mistake.
I am a mother.
You have no idea
how deep that goes.
Yeah, I have a little girl.
So, you know, I think
I have some idea here.
No, it is not the same thing.
Because if you were a mother,
you wouldn't be
sitting here right now
while your wife is bringing up
your little girl all alone.
Trust me.
I know what that's like.
Tuck.
Can I see it?
This is what you've got to look forward
to if you keep going after this.
Well, at least
I'm doing something.
Do you remember when you were
about 11 years old?
There was a boy who got murdered
over in Crix County.
I found the body.
There was a vagrant,
and he had been spotted
looking at the kids all funny.
Everybody knew it was him
who had gotten this child.
I was driving down Route 17
a few days later,
and I see that old man standing
by the side of the road
urinating in broad daylight.
I draw my service weapon,
I tell him to put his hands up,
thinking about nothing
but that child.
And then out of nowhere,
he runs into the woods.
I squeezed off three rounds.
And the scary thing is,
it didn't take much
thinking at all.
Three weeks later, they found
the man who killed that boy.
It was his stepfather
up from West Memphis.
He admitted everything.
And that man that I'd shot
had a wife and two daughters.
He had dementia
and walked off
and never came back.
Why are you telling me this?
Because I know what it costs
to take a life,
and I see where this is headed.
Sweetheart, this is not you.
Lucas.
Be right back.
- You're bonded. Come on.
- By who?
Sorry. Hey. Baby!
- Don't! Don't you "babe" me!
- Come on, what do you want me--
No. Tuck, Tuck.
I'm so sick of your shit.
Hey, he's my fucking brother.
What do you want me to do?
I'm taking Ellie,
and I'm going to my mother's.
- Tanya, talk to me. Talk to me, please.
- I'm done. I'm done, Tuck.
I'm done.
Come on.
Tuck, come on. Listen.
When I walked in on that deal,
they were talking about
getting the coke
to some guy named Lou Byers.
Lou Byers is the key
to finding Eli.
- Who?
- Lou Byers.
Byers, he works with Eli.
There's an address right here.
Look at that.
If we find him, we got him.
- I can't do this shit, man.
- What do you mean you can't do this shit?
- You're my goddamn brother!
- My girl just ran off with my kid.
All right?
What do you want me to do?
Luke.
Aah!
Quick, come on!
Grab his gun.
Let's go. Let's go!
Take point. Take point.
You boys made a big mistake
coming out here.
Here, kitty cat.
Here kitty, kitty!
Come and get!
Oh, I know these woods, boys.
I know every crick and corner.
Eli.
It's okay.
- Is Byers dead?
- No, he's alive.
- Let's get him to the barn.
- Okay.
Tony Pugilese.
I work at Bateland Scapyard.
Yeah, I got to work around,
like, 7:05 that morning.
I remember the phone rang maybe
ten minutes before Emma got there.
The office lady usually answers the phone,
but she wasn't there yet.
That's how early it was.
So I picked up the phone,
and the person on the end
of the line just hung up.
Oh, and I was talking to
my dad about the green van.
He thinks he remembers a busted-up work
van parked out behind the old Stop N Go.
Said he used to see it parked
in the garage back there.
Dixon to Woodley.
We got shots fired near Byers' property.
Repeat, we got shots fired
near Byers' property.
Luke.
Holy...
There's got to be 40
or more bricks over here.
Holy shit.
Luke.
Do you know who I am?
I'm the man of the woman you and your
friends killed at the scrapyard.
I am not happy right now.
So you're gonna tell me every
one of them names that was with you.
Do you understand me?
Do you understand me right now?
I don't know who did
the robbery.
I don't know who did the robbery.
I don't know who did--
I swear to God,
I don't know who did it.
No. No, no, no, no.
I want the names
of who was with you.
I just got the truck
for these guys.
I'm telling you,
I didn't have nothing to do with it.
Who'd you get the truck for?
No, no, no. No. Aah!
Help! Please!
Who was it?
Walt's other kid.
Sid.
Sid's running the show.
Did Sid kill her?
Eli killed the girl.
It was an accident. She--
She wasn't supposed
to be there.
They was just after the money,
but it was...
He's just doing what
his brother tells him to do.
- It's Sid.
-Shut him up now.
Don't-- don't-- don't hurt him.
Time to wake up, Eli.
Get up. Get up!
Shh, shh.
Did you? Did you?
I don't know what to say.
I've been thinking about
this moment...
...ever since she left.
What do I say to you?
You're my cousin.
And that makes me think
about my family
and how much I hate you all.
All this business,
the greed and violence,
and no justice.
I don't want to be like y'all.
I don't want to be like you.
If Emma were here right now,
she'd forgive you.
So I forgive you.
Do you know anything
about rattlesnakes?
- No.
- No?
See, the thing
about rattlesnakes is...
they avoid biting
at all costs, you know?
They try to warn you.
They try to say,
"Don't-- don't mess with me.
Leave me be."
I am a rattlesnake.
This is for Emma.
-Leave a message.
-
Just calling to tell you
that your brother's dead.
-
- I recognize that voice.
Oh. Oh, now you pick up.
You know who it is.
Something tells me you went and
opened that can of worms, didn't you?
Yeah. Yeah.
Mm. Well, then you know
how this goes, then.
Think so.
Your place or mine?
There's this little old cabin
at the end of Hillspeak Road
on the lake.
I think you know about it.
Hey.
Where'd you go, huh?
Mm-mm. No.
No, no, no, no, no.
Hey.
We can talk about this!
We can talk about--
Fuck! God damn it.
Shit.
Let's go!
You okay?
You should go.
What? What are you
talking about?
I've made my bed.
Go. You've got family.
Luke.
You remember that summer
you were probably, like, 6 or 7?
We finally put that swing set
up in the backyard.
And we'd both be out there
just every day,
almost all summer long,
swinging away.
You remember that?
One day, mom came out and she thought
you'd gone missing out in the woods.
I took off.
I'm calling your name,
just searched everywhere.
Down by the creek.
I mean, nothing.
Finally, I got back
and you'd just been asleep
in your goddamn bed
the whole time.
I never told you this, but that was the
scared-est I've ever been in my whole life,
just not knowing if I had my
little brother around anymore.
Yeah, I'm not going anywhere.
- They sweep yet?
-Yeah.
Did he tell you
who the headshot victim is?
- No.
- It's Eli Frost.
- You'll want to talk to Lucas.
- Any prints?
Nothing clean.
They're still checking the house, though.
Hey, uh, actually, I got this.
- What's this?
- It came for you. Phone records request.
- Why do you want phone records?
- Tony Pugilese said someone
called looking
for Merle Bateland
right before they robbed
the office.
So? / Said they hung up
when he asked for a message.
Ah, so you're thinking they were
casing to see if it was clear?
No, I am thinking
that whoever made that call
is now the lead suspect
at Bateland.
Hmm.
What? What?
What? What is it?
Go to the back.
Maybe it was an animal.
Woods.
They're coming in the woods.
I got two out front.
How many do you see?
One.
Hey, they're coming
in the back!
Hey! Front door.
He's coming in the front door.
Tuck!
Come on. Come on. Hey.
Ah, fuck!
Burns like a bitch.
I'll live.
You get to the boat.
No, no, no, no.
I'll hold 'em off.
Go. Keep the motor running.
Hey, half-blood.
Y'all want to talk it out?
There's nothing to talk about.
He doesn't know,
does he, Tuck?
You didn't tell him
about the girl.
Hold it! Don't move!
Oh, ain't this
a hell of a pickle.
What's he talking about, Tuck,
about the girl?
Your brother's the one
who set that job up.
It ain't true.
It ain't true, Lukey. I swear to God.
Do they know how much fucking
money you owe me?
You remember what you said.
"Nobody ever hit a scrapyard.
It'll be empty.
Cops'll never see
that one coming."
But what he didn't see coming
was your old lady
walking through the door.
That's the truth.
Your own brother's
the reason she's dead.
That's-- it's bullshit.
Luke, that's fucking bullshit.
Don't listen to him.
Is he telling the truth?
Tuck, look at me in the eye.
Were you sick that morning?
Tuck, were you sick
that morning?
I know the universe can be
awful cruel, Lucas.
Believe me, I know.
Tell me it wasn't true!
Come on, man.
I warned you.
Mind the hungry ones.
I love you, Luke.
You're my brother!
Tuck. Baby.
Lucas, no!
Lucas!
Walt!
-Whoo!
-Nice!
- God, I hate fishing.
- What?
What? You're so good
at it though.
I mean, you're the one
who loves fishing.
And if that's the trade-off,
well, baby,
I can fish all day.
I love you.
Watch this.
It's tough, this one.
You're better
at fishing than I am.
- Ooh, I didn't say I wasn't good at it.
- That's true. That's true.
I mean, imagine all the things I could do
if I put my mind to it.
There's nothing you couldn't do.
- Hey! Aah!
- What? Look at that.
Pull it in! / I mean, it's light.
It doesn't feel like a fish.
Ah, it looks like
we caught the bottom.
It got all tangled up.
Oh. Look at this. Hmm.
How long do you think
it's been in there?
I don't know.
It's in pretty good condition.
It fits.
Hey, will you marry me?
Shut up.
I won't.
Will you marry me?
Yes. Yes, so much I will.
I love you so much.
- What?
- Nothing! Okay, sit over here.
- Where?
- Sit there.
Okay. Say cheese.